Who the you calling a [ __ ] [ __ ] this
whole business of taking things in
stride and and you know showing
professionalism, all that is is language
for pacifism. That's it. They have
continuously tried to convince you that
being passive and being quiet and and
and literally just like brushing it off
your shoulder that that is a that that
is an indicator of your civility. That's
an indicator of your professionalism.
Did they know it was a Tourette's
outburst at the time? No, they didn't.
And that's not how Tourette's outburst
even worked. So this whole business of
just taking on the chin, can you spaz on
a soul person? People that have
Tourette's aren't slow. Did the person
with the Tourette's apologize?
>> They hear their ticks. They know what
they're saying. He never apologized. So
like, what are we even talking about?
That the story would have been how
Amanda cursed out the man who called her
a [ __ ] at the BAFTAs. That's what the
story would have been. Every black
person there should have left. Every
black person there should have been
like, "What? Time to go. So miss me with
all of this. It's ableless to punch
somebody for calling you a [ __ ]
because they have Tourette's. Nah,
>> I am Savvy Mike in this is a more tamed
Savvy Mike, [laughter] but no. And this
is I am Savvy Mike TV. And well, we got
Amanda Seals commenting
on the recent situation that happened at
the BAFTAs over the weekend or a few
days ago. I don't know when this when
the BAFTA was. I think it was Sunday. I
don't remember. It's Wednesday now, but
I don't I think it was a few days ago.
Yeah, I think it was Sunday night.
Either way, it's neither here nor there.
Before I get into this, let's watch the
clip of of what happened at the BAFTAs,
what she's talking about, what she's
addressing.
>> Del and I are delighted to be presenting
the first BAFTA of the night for a vital
part of movie making.
>> Do not adjust your ears. Don't adjust
your screens. You heard exactly what
everybody else did. Even them two. Look
at look at we're here. Daryl Lindo
didn't know what to do. And this is this
has sparked a lot of debate, right? A
lot of debate. Initially, what I saw at
least cruising through the webs and the
comments and the replies. I saw a lot of
black people angry. I did. And I saw a
lot of them not wanting to give this man
with Tourette's grace. Because if you
don't know, the reason he was there is
because a movie that was based off of
him and his life with Tourett syndrome
was was nominated for the BAFTAs. Uh I
think the guy that was in that movie
that was acting, he he wasn't like the
actual person, you know, he was just
acting, but he won the award for best
actor of the year for that movie. I
swear I think it would be coming to
America in about a month or two. I'll
definitely check it out. I have another
channel called Savior Reviews where I
talk about movies. if you want to see
that. I'll definitely be reviewing this
one cuz in all the clips I seen, I was
like, well, if you ask me, I I take that
performance over watching Timothy
Shalomé get smacked by pingpong on his
ass. That
really want to discuss it and talk about
it, but that's neither here nor there.
Regardless of it, this guy who the movie
was based off of was of course, I guess,
invited to the Baptists and and he
decided to attend. And during this
night, apparently this wasn't the only
outburst. This was the only one we heard
for some strange and weird reasons if we
if we can't if we can be honest because
apparently one there's a 2-hour delay
delay with this show. That's number one.
And number two, he had been blurting out
all night and all night they had been
cutting it out. But when we get to the
part where he says, "Nigga, [laughter]
all of a sudden, all of a sudden we just
forget about editing." That's that's
when that's when our editing proudness
just goes out the window, right? So,
there's been a lot of debate, a lot of
discussion. And I'm going to tell you
where I stand now because the rest of
this video is just about Amanda Sills
calling out Ryan Cougler, I guess, for
for even being a Hollywood elite amongst
these Hollywood elites and making the
movie that he made and still cowtowing
and and kissing ass to these Hollywood
elites. I'm just going to give my two
cents real quick because I I've been let
you know I've been thinking about making
a whole new channel where I just do
video essays. Been kind of inspired by
FD Signifier and and watching a lot of
his videos. A and the script I'm writing
right now is about Marty Supreme and the
problem with white privilege cuz that's
what that movie is basically about. And
it it's ironic that this happened
because I was trying to figure out a way
to kind of tie this all into what's
going on with this award stuff and and
how Mark or how Timothy Shalamé is being
propped on a pedestal anticipated to win
the best actor award at the Academyy's
over a man like Michael B. Jordan who
literally played three rows damn near in
his movie and did an amazing job doing
it. And while I'm not mad at Timothy
Shalomé getting the recognition he's
getting for Marty Supreme, because if
you ask me, he did a great job in that
movie, too. It it just it it feels odd.
The Marty Supreme and and Timothy
Shalomé went in for basically playing a
a man with egregious white privilege and
can get away and over whoever he wants
just to be the best pingpong player in
the world. And then you got this this
other movie. I forgot my point. Either
way, it's it's sad. It It's sad and it's
wrong to be honest. And it just it Oh,
and okay, I I remember my point. And
then you got one battle after another,
right? And and if you haven't seen that
movie, I'm going to basically spoil it
for you right now in in the best way. It
it's it's about immigration. It's about
ICE. Yes. But they're talking about
Shawn Penn winning best supporting actor
and Paul Thomas Anderson winning best
director and adapted screenplay, I
believe, and it overall winning best
picture. And if we could be quite
honest, the movie is basically about old
white men and impregnating [laughter]
black women and and them having to deal
with it and them [clears throat] having
to deal deal with the fact that they
like black women and and still have this
power dynamic. It's just odd. Well, I
like the last two hours of of one battle
after another. That's some peak cinema.
Them first 35 minutes was strange. It
was. And I feel like they're gonna award
Tiana Taylor for playing basically the
black woman that gets pregnant by old
white man in power. And they're gonna
award Shawn Penn for playing that old
white man. And they're going to award
Paul Thomas Anderson for making this
movie. And it's just like the optics,
but nobody's talking about it. So that's
why I'm writing this video essay in a
roundabout ways. But this happened and
and it it showed me that yeah, white
white privilege even exists in a man
with with Tourette's cuz number one, he
shouldn't have been there. He just
shouldn't have. I get the movie was
based on him and it's a big moment, big
night, whatever. He knowing his
condition he should the fact that he
will be I get we want to okay well he he
has a disability but we can't we
shouldn't be not letting people in
because they had disability but this
disability could cause problems like
this at the end of the day there should
been some forward thinking to go well
what if two black people get on the
stage and he yells [ __ ] you would think
the bath producers would go well we're
just going to cut it out like we we're
doing everything else he says but for
some reason they didn't cut that out. So
it's a lot of weirdness here. It's a lot
of strangers that's going on. And while
I understand
people saying hey we shouldn't we
shouldn't degrade the man. He has a he
has a problem he can't control. And in
that moment something happened he
couldn't control. Now, while it might
have been something he holds in and it
might be a part of his intrusive
thoughts, at the end of the day, he
can't control the fact that he said what
he said. Cool. At the end of the day, he
said it. And regardless of it, he should
have apologized.
It's BAFTA as a whole should have
apologized, not to us, but to Michael B.
Jordan and Del Roy Lindo. Those are the
two people they should have apologized
to. All I'm saying is accountab only way
this doesn't happen again is if people
take accountability.
Now, there's a lot more I could get into
when it comes to this subject as far as
white privilege goes and and the fact
that they don't have to take
accountability and we're the ones who
always have to show grace in situations
like this. Even when it comes to a man
with Tourette's or even if he doesn't
have Tourette's, if he's just some half
black, half white man that looks like a
ginger and he's saying [ __ ] 15 times in
a rap song, we're supposed to show grace
to him because, well, he got a black
daddy.
Like that's what we have to do. But when
the when it's flipped, when when it's
put on the other shoe, depending on what
shoe you want to put it on, we got to
take accountability for that. Apologize,
say we're wrong, do all types of extra.
Kanye West literally has to write a
whole letter apologizing, explaining
himself to the because that's the only
way he could quote unquote be accepted
back into society. You get what I'm
saying? Do you catch my drift? Now, if
you don't, cool. I'm not going to keep
explaining because then I might get
cancelled. But catch my drift. It's not
fair. That's all I'm saying. That we
have to show grace and the other side of
the aisle don't. We have to be
accountable and the other side of the
aisle with their white privilege can can
do stupid and up. And we let it go
because well, Marty Supreme. It all ties
back to it.
A movie about a white man who [ __ ]
everybody he loves over in that movie
just to be a pingpong player. If that's
not white privilege, I don't know what
is. Anyways, let's keep let's listen to
the last clip. I'm out of here. I'm
done.
>> And expecting racist not to happen.
Racism not to happen. Stop supporting
this. Let them crackers be amongst
themselves. You know, I I don't know why
we keep showing up to these places
expecting respect. Okay, Kurban, you had
three strikes and you are out. You had
nothing valid to say. You asked me twice
about Dr. Umar and then asked, "Would I
consider dating a man younger than me?"
Go [laughter] away. I just don't see the
point. Why? Why? Why are you going to
the Oscars, the Baptistas, like Ryan
Cougler, whose work I love
and who I respect is going to go to the
Grammy. It's going to go to the Oscars
and his whole movie is about how
assimilation is what killing black
people. He's going to go to the Oscars.
Why would you make that movie and then
show up in the places and spaces of
assimilation?
She she has a point, but that that falls
into a chapter that I have in my video
essay about ass kissing and how we kiss
ass just to get the recognition that we
deserve for our talent from these white
people. That won't show us any grace
when it comes down to anything. We We
have to be on top of everything. We have
to show up like Ryan Cougler has to show
up. He has to show up to all this just
to get awards and just to play nice with
these white people ass kissing just to
show that he's basically a part of the
program. And while he made a movie about
how black people create the program and
white people come to assimilate it and
take it and and how we create culture
and how we make culture and they just
want what we have and our art. He made a
whole movie about that. And but you got
to realize the only way he could have
made that movie is by ass kissing. He He
Ryan Cougar didn't fund Sinners. Warner
Brothers did. He had to get a green
light. People had to read the script. It
had to go through this and that and the
third. Ju just for that movie. Contracts
had to be signed. just for that movie to
even start being filmed, he had to kiss
ass. And unfortunately for us as black
people, that's what we have to do in
order to get to the plateaus that we
seek to reach the recognition that we
deserve. If you ask me, Sinners was the
best movie last year. Hands down. I seen
a lot of movies last year. It was
Sinners. Now, I still got sentimental
value to watch. Ham minute. There's some
other Oscar movies that I got. But I
highly doubt that those movies are
better than Sinners. [laughter] I just
highly doubt it. That's how good that
movie was. But in order for that movie
to even get made, ass had to get kissed.
Particularly, specifically white ass.
>> No, the best NBA player does not have to
go to the finals, no matter how racist.
and comparing playing on a team to being
somebody who has made a movie and is
funded are completely false
equivalencies. I don't even understand
why you thought that made any sense.
>> Anyways, shout out to Amanda Sills. I
[ __ ] with her. Let me know what you
think in the comments below about
everything that was said in this video.
As always, I'm Savvy Mike in this is I
am Savvy Mike TV. Peace.